onestepahead.com 2014-06-03

# Privacy Policy from One Step Ahead

What is your Privacy Policy?

One Step Ahead is in the middle of an exciting change! We’re transitioning operations to join the family of Colony Brands, which includes premier companies like Seventh Avenue, Montgomery Ward, Ginny’s, and Swiss Colony. 

**ONE STEP AHEAD AND ONESTEPAHEAD.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

Last modified January 1, 2014 

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") of OSA Brands, LLC and the OneStepAhead.com website (sometimes referred to as the "Site"). We want you to understand the types of information we gather about you, how we use it, and the steps we take to safeguard it. Throughout this policy, "One Step Ahead " means OSA Brands, LLC. Throughout this policy, "We," "Our," and "Us" means "Our Family of Companies". "Our Family of Companies" is also sometimes referred to herein as "Affiliates". Please  "click here" to see a current listing of Our Family of Companies. 

This policy applies to information collected from you at the Site. It also applies to information that We may collect from you elsewhere or by other means (for example, if you contact our customer service and/or ordering departments by mail or telephone), unless We inform you otherwise. When you provide personal information at the Site or by other means, you are consenting to the manner in which We will collect, store, use and disclose that information as set forth below. 

Our postal address is:  
OSA Brands, LLC  
1112 7th Avenue  
Monroe, WI 53566-1364

You can Email us at **[customerservice@OneStepAhead .com](mailto:customerservice@OneStepAhead%20.com)** or you can reach us by telephone at our customer service number 1-888-557-3851.

**About The Information We Collect and How We May Use It**

You are not required to provide any personal information in order to have general access to the Site. However, in order to make purchases, to access certain information, features or services at the Site or offerings of One Step Ahead, you may be required to provide certain personal information. We collect personal information about you from the following sources:

  * When you shop with One Step Ahead , including at OneStepAhead.com, We obtain from you the information that We need to complete your transaction. This information may include your name, address, telephone number and email address.
  * When you establish an account or register to use certain features at the Site.
  * If you provide us with comments or suggestions, request information about our products and services or contact our customer service or order department via phone, email or other forms of communication.
  * We may collect additional information if you choose to use or participate in one of our various services, programs or surveys. For example, if you sign up for our wish list service, We will ask you for information concerning your gift selections.
  * From time to time we may run promotions, contests or sweepstakes, and collect personal information from you if you participate in them.
  * We obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use from your transactions and other interactions with Us. We also share information with and/or receive information from Our Family of Companies and from third parties with whom we have marketing, advertising or service relationships as described below. These third party companies also may be individually or collectively referred to in this Policy as a "Third Party" or "Third Parties".
  * We also may collect information from consumer reporting agencies.

"Personal information" is information that may be used, either alone or in combination with other information, to identify you.

**How We Use Cookies and Web Beacons  
**We keep track of individual visitors to our Site through the use of "cookies", "web beacons" and other web technologies, which are individually or collectively referred to herein as "Tracking Technologies". Cookies are small files that contain a short line of text. They contain absolutely no personally identifiable information about you. These text files are sent to your Internet browser which, in turn, places information from the text file in its cookie file (you can see this file in your Internet browser). Cookies identify you as you move from page to page and allow Us to collect information to keep track of your visit. For example, cookies allow Us to know what item(s) you have placed in your shopping cart, and cookies keep that information for checkout even if you decide to leave the Site and return at a later time to finish shopping.

That is why We use Tracking Technologies, and why it is essential that, in order for you to order from our Site, you must have enabled the "accept cookies" option on your browser. We also use Tracking Technologies to select banner and other advertising that is better tailored to your interests. We hope this explanation makes sense and will allay any concerns you may have about how our Site operates. The use of Tracking Technologies is standard on the Internet and is used to make online shopping easier and quicker. You may, of course, choose not to accept cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, purchasing is not possible at the OneStepAhead .com Site. If you do not accept cookies, you may still place your order by calling us at our customer service number 800-274-8440. 

**Aggregate Information**  
We collect non-personally identifiable information about how users navigate to and through the Site, including the number of visits to the Site and specific pages visited while at the Site and the IP addresses of those visitors to the Site. We aggregate this statistical information and use it to help us administer and to enhance the Site and for research and development, user analysis and business decision making. These aggregate statistics also may be provided to Our Family of Companies and/or Third Parties to assist us with our marketing and advertising activities and/or to assist service providers in connection with the taking or processing orders or maintaining operation of the Site. 

**How We Use Personal Information**  
We use your personal information to provide products that you purchase from us and provide information you have requested. We share your personal information with Our Family of Companies and Third Parties who assist us with these efforts. For example, we use Third Party Service Providers to process credit card transactions, fulfill orders, ship products, and send emails to our customers. 

We also use personal information, including that collected from Us and Third Parties to improve the quality of the products and services that we offer to you. We also want to provide you a pleasant shopping experience on the Site. In order to do this, we continually strive to improve the services provided to you. We use the personal information obtained as one source to help us achieve this goal, by personalizing, through our communications and your visits to the Site, offers of products and services that we believe would be of interest to you. We may use the personal information that you have given to us and cross-reference it with personal information we receive from Our Family of Companies and Third Parties in order to provide you an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience. 

We also may use the services of other Third Party businesses to perform tasks for us, such as providing marketing assistance and data analysis; and We may provide personal information to those businesses when that information is necessary or desirable for them to perform such services. 

_**Marketing Consultants**_. Our marketing consultants use cookies and other Web technologies to collect information about visits to the Site. This information alone does not identify you personally. It does assist with the compilation of statistics concerning the number of visitors, the pages they visited and the links they clicked. It also tells us where visitors to the Site came from and where they go when they leave the Site. This aggregated information is used by Us to understand and adjust to the needs and desires of Our visitors. It allows us to create better content and to engineer better site functionality and usability for those visitors. Finally, this information helps us improve the effectiveness of our advertising and marketing efforts.

_**Display Advertising**_. We use Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.  We use these features to provide more relevant and targeted content both on our sites and in advertising.  Advertising features We use include remarketing, interest categories, similar audiences, other types of interest-based advertising, and demographic and location targeting.  Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the internet. We, and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on a user’s past visits to our site.  We, and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to report on how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.  We also use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising, along with third-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics, for internal research and external marketing purposes.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customized Google Display Network ads at Google Ads Settings ([www. **google**.com/ **ads** /preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences)).  More information on currently available opt-outs for Google Analytics can be [found here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) (<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>).  

_**Advertising Companies**_. We also use Third Party advertising companies to assist Us with our online advertising. These advertising companies use cookies and other Web Technologies to target and to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. When you visit the Site and other sites in their advertising network, the sites tag your computer with a "cookie." This cookie alone does not personally identify you, but it does allow the advertiser to recognize your computer when you visit any of their network sites. This permits them to target the types of ads and promotions they display to that particular computer. The intent is to display only interest-based advertisements tailored to your web preferences and usage patterns and to minimize the number of advertisements that are not relevant to or appropriate for you. How Our advertising companies use cookies and other web technologies is covered by their individual privacy policies and are not covered by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to receive our advertising companies’ cookies, you may "opt-out" by using the following link to the Network Advertising Initiative (the "NAI"). The NAI has worked with the Federal Trade Commission to develop a set of self-regulatory industry standards "The NAI Principles" that address how third party advertising networks may use information about you.  "Click here" for more information on NAI. Additional information regarding interest-based advertising and your opt-out rights can be found at [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/)’s [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) site. At the present time our Site is not configured to automatically respond to “do not track” signals or similar mechanisms to indicate you do not wish to be tracked or receive interest-based ads, however, you have other methods of opting-out of interest-based advertisements as described above. 

**Opting out of Receiving Catalogs or Promotional Material**  
If you no longer wish to receive our catalogs or promotional emails, you may call Us at 1-888-557-3851 to make arrangements for those mailings to be discontinued. Also, as a member of the Direct Marketing Association, we comply with its requirements for consumer choice, including its Commitment to Consumer Choice and DMA choice programs, and honor opt-outs from marketing communications through those programs. You can find more information about the DMA and its Commitment to Consumer Choice at: **www.the-dma.org** ; **www.dmaccc.org** ; and **www.dmachoice.org**. Please understand that it may take a period of several weeks for any requested changes through these procedures to take effect and for such mailings to be discontinued. [For opting out of promotional emails, see also the section "Email Communications below". Note, however, that You may not opt out of receiving transactional emails.] 

**Legal Requirements**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when We believe that disclosure is necessary to protect Our rights and/or to comply with a judicial or administrative proceeding, court or governmental order, or legal process served on Us. We also may share information when We have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to prevent harm to One Step Ahead, Our Family of Companies, the Site, or Our customers. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts, or other government entities. 

**Opting Out of Personal Information Sharing**   
If you prefer that One Step Ahead does not share certain personal information about you with third party (non-Affiliate) companies for the purpose of them marketing their own services or products to you, you can direct us not to share that information (that is, opt out of the sharing) by calling us at One Step Ahead or writing us at Credit Department, 1112 7th Avenue, Monroe, WI 53566. You must give us enough information so that we can locate your information and take action. To opt out of third party online advertising, see the sub-section on Advertising Companies above. 

**Accessing, Correcting, and Amending Your Personal Information**  
One Step Ahead provides you access to your account at OneStepAhead .com. In order to view your account information please click the "Your Account" link at the top of the home page. From this link, you can view and change some of the personal information that We have collected from you (such as mailing address, stored credit cards, wish list and address book). From the account page, you may also change your subscription settings in order to change whether or not you receive promotional emails from One Step Ahead . One Step Ahead also provides you access to certain other personal information that We have collected from you. If you believe that the personal information that We have collected from you, which you cannot access through your account page, is inaccurate and needs to be changed or amended, you can inform us of this by calling us at 1-888-557-3851 or writing us at Credit Dept., 1112 7th Avenue, Monroe, WI 53566. 

**Email Communications**  
You may be contacted via email by One Step Ahead regarding your order, your account or certain other matters. Typically, we send two types of email communications. You may receive transactional emails that provide you with information about your order such as order acknowledgements and confirmations, order numbers, access to the status of your order, notification of shipment and other related information, or other notifications concerning our business relationship. Since we need to communicate this information to you, you will not be able to opt out of such transactional emails. In addition to the transactional emails described above, you also may receive certain promotional email communications unless you have opted out of receiving them. All such promotional email communications will provide you with the option to opt out and thereby not receive such promotions and related promotional email communications in the future.

**OneStepAhead .com Customer Transaction Security**  
When you use a credit or debit card or other forms of online payment to make a purchase at OneStepAhead .com, We use Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information (including your card number). SSL technology is an industry standard for secure online transactions. If you would prefer to use the phone, please call our customer service number at One Step Ahead and one of Our customer service associates will gladly assist you with your order. 

**Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information**  
We maintain security practices designed to protect the security, integrity and confidentiality of customer information. We restrict access to your personal information to those employees who need access to that information to provide products or services to you. Our servers are located in the United States, and We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your personal information. 

**No Liability for Acts of Third Parties**  
We maintain safeguards to protect the confidentiality of customer personal information. However, transmissions protected by security technology and implemented by human beings cannot be made absolutely secure. Consequently, We shall not be liable for unauthorized disclosure of personal information due to no fault of One Step Ahead , including, but not limited to, errors in transmission and unauthorized acts of the staffs of One Step Ahead or Our Family of Companies and/or Third Parties.

**Mergers and Acquisitions**  
Circumstances may arise where, for business reasons, We decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize Our businesses. Such a transaction may involve the transfer and disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers and/or receipt of such information from sellers. In the event that another party acquires some or all of Our Family of Companies or a division or portion thereof, personal information would be a business asset acquired from Us that could be transferred to the buyer. 

**Children's Privacy**  
One Step Ahead does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. We also do not knowingly post content provided by minors such as reviews, comments, or blog posts. If you believe we might have any information or content from a child under the age of 13, please contact us by telephone at [One Step Ahead](http://www.onestepahead.com/) or email at [customerservice@OneStepAhead .com](mailto:customerservice@OneStepAhead%20.com). 

**User Submissions**  
If you participate in a discussion forum or post messages to a bulletin board at the Site, such as product reviews, you should be aware that the information disclosed and shared will be broadly available to other people, both inside and outside of One Step Ahead , who have access to OneStepAhead .com. Any participant's expressed opinion in a forum or bulletin board is his or her own and should not be considered as reflecting the opinion of One Step Ahead or Our Family of Companies. One Step Ahead reserves the right to moderate any message or comment posted on the Site and to remove any message or comment that is offensive, profane or otherwise inappropriate in the discretion of One Step Ahead. 

**Links to Other Sites; Third Party Technology Interfaces; and Applications**  
While visiting the Site you may have the opportunity to link to, interact with, or receive content from websites operated by our business partners or other third parties. Those sites may be co-branded or may have the look and feel of being on our site, but are not our Site, not under our control, and therefore not subject to this Privacy Policy. If you are asked to provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links or widgets from the Site. Therefore, we strongly recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit. We encourage you to read the policy of other sites before submitting any personal information. If you are utilizing a third party application when you visit the Site, such third party application may, as part of its functionality, provide information about your visit to Us or to others, subject to the terms and conditions of use of such application and/or the privacy policy of such application. Accordingly, you are encouraged to familiarize yourself with the ways in which such applications may be used to collect and to disseminate data and personal information. 

**Updates to our Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to amend this policy from time to time and to apply any changes to information previously collected as permitted by law. If we amend our Privacy Policy in any material way, we will post those changes on the Site. (Changes in contact information or minor typographical errors will simply be corrected on the Site.) Please check back periodically to view this Privacy Policy as you continue to use our Site. 

**Applicability of Privacy Policy**  
If you set up an account at One Step Ahead , make a purchase through the Site or through any of Our Family of Companies websites, or submit any personal information to Us by signing up for any of Our products or services or availing yourself of any Site feature that requires you to submit personal information, your action is deemed acceptance of Our practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you cease to be Our customer, such as when your account is closed or becomes inactive, Our information practices in this policy, as amended from time to time, will continue to apply. 

Any dispute over privacy matters between you and One Step Ahead is subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and to One Step Ahead ’s Terms of Use, which is incorporated herein and can be read by 

_clicking here_

.
